I woke up out of my sleep just to ask y'all, why are you talking about voting rights being gutted
as if voting rights haven't been gutted for like entire swaths of people for a very long time?
You're talking about voting rights being gutted like slavery ain't been on the books this whole
time. Like disenfranchisement because of being incarcerated hasn't been on the books this whole
time. You're talking about voting rights being gutted like it hasn't been being gutted since 2003
and you just now finding out about it. So where the hell were your trusted Democrats this whole
goddamn time? Don't talk to me about, oh my God, I can't believe voting rights are being gutted.
When the truth of the matter is that slavery was never taken off the books and every single time
they have criminalized things. They have created new ways to put people in prison.
They have continued to legitimize slavery as a means of keeping this country going.
So when you come and talk about voting rights,
you just sound to me like you only give a damn about yourself. Because at the end of the day,
this has been a nation grounded in slavery and it never stopped. Even when black people got allowed
to be Democrats. I'm going back to bed.